(Leonard:)Really?
(Leonard:)You're going to risk getting
sleepy in the middle of your
(Leonard:)thermodynamic
fluctuations seminar?
(Leonard:)You know what happens
when you yawn in public.
(Sheldon:)Everyone will see
my oddly shaped uvula.
(Leonard:)You don't want that, do you?
(Sheldon:)No.
(Sheldon:)But it's a shame our society
mocks the differently uvulated.
(Sheldon:)Who was at the door?
(Leonard:)Uh, building manager.
(Leonard:)They have to fix a pipe,
so the water'll be off
tomorrow from noon to 2:00.
(Sheldon:)That's unacceptable.
(Sheldon:)We're supposed to be
given written notice.
Well, no, it doesn't matter--
we'll be at work.
(Sheldon:)What if I spill tomato
soup on my shirt,
(Sheldon:)and have to come home to change,
(Sheldon:)only to find there's no water
for an enzyme soak?
(Leonard:)Bifurcated uvula, Sheldon!
(Sheldon:)I'll have the chicken noodle.
Good night!
(Raj:)We're going
to have to be very quiet.